WASIM ULLAH

Digital Marketer

Email: wasim.ullah@aol.com Cell: 055-756-8805 Website: wasim.co Visa Status: Work Visa Expiry Date: December 31, 2019 Location: Dubai

■ CAREER SUMMARY

With extensive experience in building strong brand presence across all the digital media platforms with a sales funnel approach, I craft and implement successful digital marketing strategies that shape a business growth. With a degree in business, certifications in digital marketing and powerful creative acumen, I cherish an ethical results driven approach to growth hacking.

■ ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

1. GrowthMaster from Growth University	Nov 2018
2. Digital Marketing Circuit from General Assembly	Oct 2018 - Nov 2018
3. Startup Founder Track from Startup School by Y Combinator	Sep 2018 - Nov 2018
4. BBA (Hons.) from University of the Punjab	Sep 2009 – Sep 2013

■ PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1. Senior Digital Branding Specialist at Vudu Advertising	Feb 2018 – Present
2. Digital Media Lead at CFE Group of Colleges	Jun 2015 – Jul 2017
3. Marketing Associate at Imanagers	Dec 2013 – Apr 2015

■ PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

1. Search Engine Optimization	2. Graphic Designing	Video Editing
4. Social Media Marketing	5. Paid Advertising	6. Content Writing
7. Website Management	8. Data Analytics	9. Email Marketing
10. Website Development		

■ INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

1. Corporate Training at Zia Associates	2. Digital Branding for Aqua Safe Group
3. Digital Branding for Schuitema Pakistan	4. Search Engine Strategy for IPS

■ PERSONAL DETAILS

Marital Status:	Single	Date of Birth:	December 11, 1992
Nationality:	Pakistani	Passport:	CP6853621